[
  {
    "question": "Identify the passive voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"They know me.\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "I am known to them.",
    "optionB": "I am known by them.",
    "optionC": "I are known to them.",
    "optionD": "I is known to them.",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "A. I am known to them.",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for passive voice: Subject (Object of Active) + Helping Verb + Past Participle (V3) + by + Object (Subject of Active).",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the passive voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"He invited me to his house yesterday.\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "I am invited to his house tomorrow.",
    "optionB": "I am invited to his house today.",
    "optionC": "I was invited to his house yesterday.",
    "optionD": "He was invited to his house yesterday by me.",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "C. I was invited to his house yesterday.",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for passive voice: Subject (Object of Active) + Helping Verb + Past Participle (V3) + by + Object (Subject of Active).",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the passive voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"All desire wealth and some acquire it.\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "Wealth was acquired and desired.",
    "optionB": "Wealth is acquired and desired by some.",
    "optionC": "Wealth is desired and acquired by none.",
    "optionD": "Wealth is desired by all and acquired by some.",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "D. Wealth is desired by all and acquired by some.",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for passive voice: Subject (Object of Active) + Helping Verb + Past Participle (V3) + by + Object (Subject of Active).",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the passive voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"You must endure what you cannot cure.\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "What can be cured must be endured.",
    "optionB": "What cannot be cured must not be endured.",
    "optionC": "What cannot be cured must be endured.",
    "optionD": "What can be cured must not be endured.",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "C. What cannot be cured must be endured.",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for passive voice: Subject (Object of Active) + Helping Verb + Past Participle (V3) + by + Object (Subject of Active).",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the passive voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"We must listen to his words.\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "His words must be listened to.",
    "optionB": "Words must be listened by us.",
    "optionC": "His words must be listened.",
    "optionD": "His words must not be listened.",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "C. His words must be listened.",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for passive voice: Subject (Object of Active) + Helping Verb + Past Participle (V3) + by + Object (Subject of Active).",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the active voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"Our army has been defeated.\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "The enemy has defeated our army.",
    "optionB": "Army defeated.",
    "optionC": "The enemy was defeated by our army.",
    "optionD": "The enemy has won the battle.",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "B. Army defeated.",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for active voice: Subject + Verb + Object.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the active voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"I know her.\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "She knows me.",
    "optionB": "She is known to me.",
    "optionC": "I am known to her.",
    "optionD": "She does not know me.",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "B. She is known to me.",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for active voice: Subject + Verb + Object.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the active voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"We shall be blamed by everyone.\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "Everyone shall blame we.",
    "optionB": "We shall blame everyone.",
    "optionC": "Everyone will blame us.",
    "optionD": "Everyone will be blamed by us.",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "C. Everyone will blame us.",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for active voice: Subject + Verb + Object.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the active voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"The ship was set on fire and abandoned by the crew.\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "The crew set the ship on fire and abandoned ship.",
    "optionB": "The crew set the ship on fire and abandoned it.",
    "optionC": "The crew set it on fire and abandoned ship.",
    "optionD": "The crew set on fire and abandoned ship.",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "B. The crew set the ship on fire and abandoned it.",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for active voice: Subject + Verb + Object.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Identify the active voice for the given sentence. <br/>\"Why should I be suspected by you?\"",
    "questionHasImg": false,
    "questionImg": "",
    "optionA": "Why should you suspect me?",
    "optionB": "Why should you not suspect me?",
    "optionC": "Why should I be the suspect?",
    "optionD": "Why should I suspect you?",
    "isOptionsHaveImages": [false, false, false, false],
    "optionAImg": "",
    "optionBImg": "",
    "optionCImg": "",
    "optionDImg": "",
    "answer": "D. Why should I suspect you?",
    "explanation": "Wrong answer! Sentence structure for active voice: Subject + Verb + Object.",
    "explanationHasImg": false,
    "explanationImg": "",
    "noOfAttempts": 2,
    "questionType": "selectOptions",
    "maxMarks": 1
  }
]
